Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series IV: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Moving Images, 2004-2005
  - Subseries II: The History Channel, 2004, 188 videocassettes (miniDV)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV275, 1 miniDV
      - Event in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Lesstell Chickie James interviewed by Dan Lewis in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
    - AFC 2005/015: MV276, 1 miniDV
      - Paul Frances interviewed by Dan Lewis in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Event in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV277, 1 miniDV
      - Event in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV278, 1 miniDV
      - Musical tribute to Motown in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV279, 1 miniDV
      - Anna Langford interviewed by Dan Lewis in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Ruth A. Loggins interviewed by Dan Lewis in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Elizabeth Upshaw interviewed by Dan Lewis in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV280, 1 miniDV
      - Event in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
      - Event in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV281, 1 miniDV
      - Gregory B. Dawson interviewed in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
      - Brenda McClelland interviewed in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV282, 1 miniDV
      - Ruth Bledsoe interviewed by Andy Bowley in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: MV283, 1 miniDV
      - Willie Inez Brown interviewed in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
      - Bus ride in Chicago, Illinois, 2004-10-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV284, 1 miniDV
      - Percy Green, II, interviewed in St. Louis, Missouri, 2004-10-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV285, 1 miniDV
      - Imogene Player interviewed in Topeka, Kansas, 2004-10-04
  - Subseries III: Transcripts, 2004, 96 transcripts in 47 folders
    - Brian Taylor interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 31/35)
      See related video
    - Geraldine Phillips interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 31/36)
    - Audrey Straus Koch interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 31/36)
    - Florence Orbech interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 31/36)
    - Mary Y. Betters interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 31/36)
    - Mary Y. Betters interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 31/37)
    - Betty Bunce interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 > (Box-folder 31/37)
    - Elbert Ransom, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 31/37)
    - J. Samuel Williams, Jr. interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/38)
    - Doug Wilder interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/38)
    - Bob Cohen interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/38)
    - Jacqueline Dash Ziglar interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/39)
    - Willie C. Jones interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/39)
    - Hugo A. Owens interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 31/39)
    - Hugo A. Owens interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 31/40)
    - Paula Owens Parker interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (Box-folder 31/40)
    - Thad Woodard interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (Box-folder 31/41)
    - Helen O'Brien interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (Box-folder 31/41)
    - Raymond Whitsell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 31/41)
    - Raymond Whitsell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 31/42)
    - Garland Knott interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (Box-folder 31/43)
    - Fay Mayo interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (Box-folder 31/43)
    - Jean Scales interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (Box-folder 31/43)
    - Linda Beatrice Brown interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (Box-folder 31/44)
    - Doxie Whitfield interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (Box-folder 31/44)
    - James Wyckoff interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Frederick Beckner interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Anthony Layng interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Joyce Johnson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Nelson Johnson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Vernon King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Vernon King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Brumit B. DeLaine interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Joseph Jackson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Gretchen Weber interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Gretchen Weber interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Violet Staley interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Cleveland Sellers interviewed by Andy Bowley in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - George R. Dean interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/7)
    - George R. Dean (2 of 2) interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Charles Smith interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Roddrick Moorer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Patricia Due interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Patricia Due interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Fred D. Lee interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - James Colbert interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/10)
    - James Colbert interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Kenneth Mullinax interviewed by Andy Bowley in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Billie Sue Hulsey interviewed by Andy Bowley in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Warren Brown interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Velma May McNear interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Ernest B. Terrell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Scott B. Smith, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Valda Harris-Montgomery interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Willie L. Robinson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - London Branch interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Mrs. A. M. E. Logan interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Jean Butler interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Edwin King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Edwin King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Gene C. Young interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Bruce Boynton interviewed by Andy Bowley in Selma, Alabama, 2004-08-16 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Betty Strong interviewed by Andy Bowley in Selma, Alabama, 2004-08-16 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Bill Minor interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22 (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Johnny Devrouax interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Johnny Devrouax interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/20)
    - Johnnie Young interviewed by Andy Bowley in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-22 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Grace Booth interviewed by Andy Bowley in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Ellie J. Dahmer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Ellie J. Dahmer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Bettie Dahmer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2004-08-23 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Dena C. Y. Bordelon interviewed by Andy Bowley in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Carolyn Pons interviewed by Andy Bowley in New Orleans, Louisiana, 2004-08-24 (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Billy Roy Pitts interviewed by Andy Bowley in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/25)
    - Billy Roy Pitts interviewed by Andy Bowley in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/26)
    - Bob Lawrence interviewed by Andy Bowley in Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2004-08-31 (Box-folder 32/27)
    - Jane VanderVeer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (Box-folder 32/28)
    - Jim Frykdahl interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/28)
    - Jim Frykdahl interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/29)
    - Emerald O'Leary interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (Box-folder 32/29)
    - Carol Ruth Silver interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (Box-folder 32/29)
    - Charles Aikens interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (Box-folder 32/30)
    - Alexander Weiss interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/30)
    - Alexander Weiss interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/31)
    - Evelio Grillo interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04 (Box-folder 32/31)
    - Claire Wahrhaftig-Isaacs interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/32)
    - Claire Wahrhaftig-Isaacs interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/33)
    - Mfalme Nguni interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (Box-folder 32/33)
    - Stephen Bingham interviewed by Andy Bowley in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (Box-folder 32/33)
    - C. Tasmiya King-Miller interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (part 3 only) (Box-folder 32/34)
    - James Peterson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08 (Box-folder 32/35)
    - Celes King, IV, interviewed by Andy Bowley in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11 (Box-folder 32/36)
    - Michael Dizaar interviewed by Andy Bowley in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 32/36)
    - Michael Dizaar interviewed by Andy Bowley in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 32/37)
    - Jean Desmond interviewed by Andy Bowley in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12 (Box-folder 32/38)
    - Claude A. Liggins interviewed by Andy Bowley in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12 (Box-folder 32/38)
  - Subseries IV: Promotional and Miscellaneous, 2004-2005, 16 videocassettes (VHS), 1 videocassette (miniDV), 2 video discs (DVD)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV286, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Brown v. Board of Education, MSNBC
    - AFC 2005/015: MV287, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Civil Rights Movement: Then & Now
    - AFC 2005/015: MV288, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Civil Rights Project
    - AFC 2005/015: MV289, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Voices of the Civil Rights Movement: Video and Member Event
    - AFC 2005/015: MV290, 1 VHS
      - Maryland Public Television, People of Brown
    - AFC 2005/015: MV291, 1 VHS
      - AARP, CBS Civil Rights Special, Re-edit
    - AFC 2005/015: MV292, 1 VHS
      - Alabama Public Television, For the Record
    - AFC 2005/015: MV293, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Broadcast News, Civil Rights: Brown VS. Board, 2004-05-11
    - AFC 2005/015: MV294, 1 VHS
      - GMA Dorothy Counts
      - Power in the Story
      - Civil Rights: Beard vs. Board
      - Lift Every Voice
    - AFC 2005/015: MV295, 1 VHS
      - AARP, How Powerful Is The Story?
    - AFC 2005/015: MV296, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Dorothy Height: A Woman of Excellence
    - AFC 2005/015: MV297, 1 VHS
      - The History Channel, THC-AARP-VOCR-TAG (1)(2)(3)-'05 revised
    - AFC 2005/015: MV298, 1 VHS
      - AARP, Voices of Civil Rights, Library of Congress Final Event, 2005-03-17
    - AFC 2005/015: MV299, 1 VHS
      - The History Channel, Voices of The Civil Rights -- AARP Vignettes, 2005-01-21
    - AFC 2005/015: MV300, 1 VHS
      - Hattiesburg High School's presentation of Freedom Summer [See Series I: Marks, Michael]
    - AFC 2005/015: MV301, 1 VHS
      - Andrew J. Brown Documentary submitted by Dr. Thomas L. Brown
    - AFC 2005/015: MV302, 1 miniDV
      - Desmond Tutu, Library of Congress, 2005-02
    - AFC 2005/015: MV303, 1 DVD
      - Voices of Civil Rights, Library of Congress Dedication Ceremony, 2005-03-17
    - AFC 2005/015: MV304, 1 DVD
      - The History Channel, Save Our History, Voices of Civil Rights
    - AFC 2005/015: MV305, 1 .mpg file
      - We Walk with the Wind
- Series V: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Graphic Images, 2004-2005
  - Preservation photocopies of original negative sleeves, 80 black and white photocopies (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Preservation photocopies of labels from CD-Rs containing digital photographs, 38 black-and-white photocopies (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Interviewee Tony Gallegos, 2 color prints: (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Interviewees in Gee's Bend, Alabama, 15 color prints: (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Selected printouts with captions from digital copies of film negatives (1 of 2), 114 black-and-white printouts (Box-folder 33/5)
    Original negatives available in binder. The CD with digital photo copies is unavailable.
  - Selected printouts with captions from digital copies of film negatives (2 of 2), 121 black-and-white printouts (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 0939-0943 and 0958, 6 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/7)
    Original negatives available in binder.
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 1048 and 1050-1051, 3 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/8)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 1125-1140, 16 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/9)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 1793-1817, 25 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 4010, 4041-4049 and 4051-4078, 39 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/11)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 5734-5773 and 5780, 40 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/12)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 6896-6902, 6904-6906 and 6908-6915, 18 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/13)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 9566-9574, 9578-9583 and 9588-9597, 25 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/14)
  - Contact sheets of negative film rolls 79797-79801, 79807, 79809-79810, 79814 and 79179-79843, 34 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 33/15)
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Alabama (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Birmingham, Alabama (1 of 2), 10 color .jpg files
      Black and white printouts also available.
    - Birmingham, Alabama (2 of 2), 27 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Montgomery, Alabama, 9 color .jpg files
    - Selma, Alabama, 21 black-and-white .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Arizona (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Fort McDowell, Arizona, 13 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Fort McDowell, Arizona, 11 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Arkansas (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas, 15 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in California (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Los Angeles, California, 10 color .jpg files
    - Modesto, California, 11 color .jpg files
    - Oakland, California (1 of 4), 10 color .jpg files
    - Oakland, California (2 of 4), 14 color .jpg files
    - Oakland, California (3 of 4), 27 color .jpg files
    - Oakland, California (4 of 4), 17 black-and-white .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in the District of Columbia (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Washington, D.C., 1 color .jpg file
      Black and white printout also available.
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Florida (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Tallahassee, Florida (1 of 2), 12 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Tallahassee, Florida (2 of 2), 72 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Georgia (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Albany, Georgia (1 of 2), 14 color .jpg file
    - Albany, Georgia (2 of 2), 12 color .jpg files
    - Macon, Georgia (1 of 2), 11 color .jpg files
    - Macon, Georgia (2 of 2), 18 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Illinois (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Chicago, Illinois (1 of 3), 11 color .jpg files
    - Chicago, Illinois (2 of 3), 21 color .jpg files
    - Chicago, Illinois (3 of 3), 34 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Indiana (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Indianapolis, Indiana, 11 color .jpg files
    - New Albany, Indiana (1 of 2), 19 color .jpg files
    - New Albany, Indiana (2 of 2), 4 black-and-white and 23 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Kansas (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Topeka, Kansas, 13 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Louisiana (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Baton Rouge, Louisiana (1 of 2), 3 color .jpg files
    - Baton Rouge, Louisiana (2 of 2), 9 black-and-white .jpg files
    - New Orleans, Louisiana, 21 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Michigan (Box-folder 34/12)
    - Detroit, Michigan, 14 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Mississippi (Box-folder 34/13)
    - Hattiesburg, Mississippi (1 of 2), 12 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Hattiesburg, Mississippi (2 of 2), 11 color .jpg files
    - Jackson, Mississippi (1 of 2), 7 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Mayerville, Mississippi, 8 color .jpg files
    - Natchez, Mississippi, 8 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Missouri (Box-folder 34/14)
    - St. Louis, Missouri, 13 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Nevada (Box-folder 34/15)
    - Las Vegas, Nevada, 40 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in New Mexico (Box-folder 34/16)
    - Hobbs, New Mexico (1 of 2), 11 color .jpg files
    - Hobbs, New Mexico (2 of 2), 23 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Santa Fe, New Mexico (1 of 2), 12 color .jpg files
    - Santa Fe, New Mexico (2 of 2), 14 black-and-white .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in North Carolina (Box-folder 34/17)
    - Charlotte, North Carolina, 9 color .tif files
    - Durham, North Carolina (1 of 2), 3 color .jpg files
    - Durham, North Carolina (2 of 2), 9 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Greensboro, North Carolina (1 of 2), 15 color .tif files
    - Greensboro, North Carolina (2 of 2), 16 color .tif files
    - Raleigh, North Carolina (1 of 3), 14 color .jpg files
    - Raleigh, North Carolina (2 of 3), 14 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Raleigh, North Carolina (3 of 3), 12 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Ohio (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Columbus, Ohio, 10 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in South Carolina (Box-folder 35/2)
    - South Carolina State Museum, Columbia, South Carolina, 15 color .jpg files
    - African American history monument at the State Capitol, Columbia, South Carolina, 6 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Columbia, South Carolina (1 of 2), 7 color .jpg and 6 color .tif files
    - Columbia, South Carolina (2 of 2), 20 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Greenfield Farm in Rembert, South Carolina, 6 black-and-white and 8 color .jpg files
    - Manning, South Carolina, 4 color .jpg files
    - Orangeburg, South Carolina, 15 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Orangeburg and Columbia, South Carolina, 16 color .jpg files
    - Summerton and Columbia, South Carolina, 32 color .jpg files
    - Summerton, South Carolina, 9 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Sumter, South Carolina, 4 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Tennessee (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Memphis, Tennessee, 30 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Health center in Memphis, Tennessee, 18 color .jpg files
    - Museum in Memphis, Tennessee, 12 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Texas (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Houston, Texas (1 of 2), 27 black-and-white .jpg files
    - Houston, Texas (2 of 2), 17 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Virginia (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Richmond, Virginia, 15 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in Wisconsin (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 16 color .jpg files
  - Photographs from bus tour events in unidentified locations, 163 black-and-white .jpg files (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Photographs of other events (Box-folder 35/8)
    - My Soul Looks Back in Wonder book party, 39 color .jpg file
    - Lunch event at the Library of Congress, 140 color .jpg file
  - Film negatives in green binder, 234 rolls of color negatives (ca. 8000 images)
Additional Guides
Summary content descriptions for some items are available in the American Folklife Center Reading Room.
Index of Cities on Bus Tour and Related Events
Albany (Ga.)
Atlanta (Ga.)
Baton Rouge (La.)
Birmingham (Ala.)
Byram (Miss.)
Charlotte (N.C.)
Chicago (Ill.)
Clyo (Ga.)
Columbia (S.C.)
Columbus (Ohio)
Conway (Ark.)
Dallas (Tex.)
Detroit (Mich.)
Durham (N.C.)
Emporia (Kan.)
Espanola (N.M.)
Farmville (Va.)
Fort McDowell (Ariz.)
Greensboro (N.C.)
Hattiesburg (Miss.)
Hayneville (Ala.)
Hempstead (Tex.)
Hilton Head (S.C.)
Hobbs (N.M.)
Houston (Tex.)
Indianapolis (Ind.)
Jackson (Miss.)
Las Vegas (Nev.)
Lawrence (Kan.)
Leighton, (Ala.)
Little Rock (Ark.)
Los Angeles (Calif.)
Macon (Ga.)
Memphis (Tenn.)
Milwaukee (Wis.)
Modesto (Calif.)
Montgomery (Ala.)
Natchez (Miss.)
New Albany (Ind.)
New Orleans (La.)
Normandy (Mo.)
Oakland (Calif.)
Orangeburg (S.C.)
Philadelphia (Miss.)
Raleigh (N.C.)
Richmond (Va.)
Ridgeland (Miss.)
Russellville (Ark.)
Saint Louis (Mo.)
San Antonio (Tex.)
Sellersburg (Ind.)
Selma (Ala.)
Shawnee (Kan.)
Springfield (Ohio)
Summerton (S.C.)
Tallahassee (Fla.)
Topeka (Kan.)
Tougaloo (Miss.)
Washington, (D.C.)
Wauwatosa (Wis.)